(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-07-28T18:26:04.218235",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
ホロライブファンクラブ！
Hololive Fan Club!
一条莉々華だよ！
I'm Ririka Ichijo!
I'm Mori Calliope!
ホロライブファンクラブ、始めました！
The hololive OFFICIAL FAN CLUB has started!
ここだけのオリジナルグッズやチケット先行抽選！
Exclusive original goods and ticket advance lottery!
他にも楽しいコンテンツがいっぱい！
Plus tons of other fun content!
Campaigns too? That sounds really fun! I'm curious!
さあみんな！
Now everyone,
ホロライブファンクラブで一緒に楽しもう！
let's have fun together in the Hololive Fan Club!
Join us now!
ここは露天風呂が有名だって言うからずっと気になってたんだよね～！
They say the open-air bath here is famous, so I've been curious about it!
……ね、キミも一緒に行かない？
Say... won't you come with me?
えっ！？一緒に「入る」って意味じゃないよ！？
Eh?! I don't mean getting in together?!
おーそーじ！モココ、大掃除やってみたいんだよね！
Big. Big. Clean. Up! I want to try this "Big Cleanup" thing!
もちろんキミも一緒にやるんだよ！？
And of course, you'll be joining me!
じゃあさっそく大掃除、開始だー！
In that case, let the big cleanup begin!
え～？服のすきまがどうしたって～？
Eh~? What's that about the gaps in my clothes~?
僕が掃除してる間に、キミはいったいどこを見てたのかな～？
While I was cleaning, just where were you looking~?
お～！ここが夢にまで見た日本の温泉町～♪
Wow! I've always dreamed of going to Japan's hot springs districts!
ん？もしかして……私と一緒にい入りたいなとか、思ってる？
Hm? Could it be... you're hoping to get in together with me?
……いいよ、一緒に、入ろうか……？
......You know what? Sure, let's go there...
って、やばいやばい！みんなそろそろカウントダウン始まるよ！
Wait, oh no oh no! Everyone, the countdown is starting soon!
あけましておめでとうございます！今年もよろしくお願いします！
Happy New Year! I look forward to working with you this year too!
えへへ……なんか改めてかしこまると、恥ずかしくって照れちゃうね♪
Ehehe... somehow when we get formal like this, it's embarrassing and makes me blush♪
ダイヤモンド富士って言うんだっけ？
Was it called Diamond Fuji?
ほらほら！だんだん富士山の輪郭が見えてきたよ！
Look look! The outline of Mt. Fuji is gradually coming into view!
なんだかもうこの景色だけで感動するよ～！
Somehow just this scenery alone is so moving~!
突然ですが、おせちを作まーす！つまみぐいしちゃだめだよ♪
This is sudden, but I'll be making osechi! And no sneaking a bite, you hear?
もしつまみぐいしちゃったら……ガブッしちゃうからねっ！？
If you do sneak a bite... I'll take a big chomp out of you!
おめでとー！おめでとー！
Happy New Year! Happy New Year!
キミとぎゅーしながらお祝い♪
Celebrating while hugging you♪
キミをぎゅーできるのはモココだけなんだから！
I'm the only one that can hug you!
ほらほらキミもモココのことぎゅーして！
C'mon, now it's your turn to hug me back!
せーの！今年もよろしくお願いします！
Ready, set! We look forward to working with you this year too!
ホロライブ3期生
hololive 3rd Generation
次に挑む舞台は
The stage we take on next
大作戦？
is a grand operation!?
「好き」と「かわいい」を詰め込んで あなたと作る大作戦！
Packing in our favorites and cuteness,
a grand operation made with you!
いっぱいのこれまでと、ときめくような一瞬を！
With all our memories so far,
and moments that make your heart flutter!
どこまででもいけちゃう気がするっ
I feel like we can go anywhere together!
ちなみに作戦の内容は
By the way, the details of the operation are...
とにかく可愛い！可愛いに満たされろ！
Above all, super cute!
Be filled with cuteness!
搭載 V8 エンジン
Packin' a V8 engine
第7感持ってる原人
And a seventh sense for things
ロックするこの世界と全人類
Rockin' this world and all humanity
この5人でゲームは前進
With us five, the game is moving forward
鳴らす4輪発射セオ
Burn the four wheels, floor the pedal
皆さんサンキュー散乱ヘオ
Thank you all three-fold, sarang hae yo
操る2台のturntable
Spinning two turntables like a pro
獲る1番ここground 0
Becoming number one, starting here, ground zero
(aye)
(Ayy)
リスク超えて挑戦
Face the risks and stand up
チャンスもセットだ当然
With chances, you can't mess up
登り上げる頂点
Going to the top, all the way up
座布団積んでく笑点
We even bring the laughs in stand-up
乗り込むFG ROADSTER
Jumping into an FG Roadster
特殊部隊集合能力者
We got a special unit full of espers
この歴史に名を刻む彫刻家
Making history, the world's a beholder
ぶっちぎりでおきざり後続車
Leaving in the dust, anyone slower
今高速でぶち抜けていく大気圏
Speeding through the stratosphere
エンジンからジェットの炎
Our jet engines thrusting, the flair of pioneers
揺れている怪気炎
Flourishing with fiery passion
眼下に見る大地を超えていく回帰線
Crossing the tropics down below
バックミラーにbig blueが映ってる ibm
Big blue reflecting in the rearview, IBM
(fire!)
打ち上げ台から飛んでくうちら世代
Taking off from the launch pad, our generation
この燃料朽ち果てないです金が
Our fuel won't ever run dry, be glad
銀河で寿司食べたい
We wanna eat sushi in the galaxy
見えてるでかいビジョン
We got a massive vision
燃えてるメンバー一同
All of us burning with passion
ただいま現在進行形
And as of this moment
超えてく世界規模
We're going above and beyond
叶うはずはwon't stop
Dreams come true, we won't stop
心臓がモンスター
Our hearts are a monster
aliens turn it up
fg party hard
光るtesla roadster
Blingin' Tesla Roadster
heavy booster
目覚めていく本能
Awakening the instincts
青い炎
Blue blazes
bff let's go out , so get in the car
BFF, let's go out, so get in the car
0から宇宙まで囚われず
Prisoners to nothing, from naught to all creation
走るfg roadster
Speeding the FG Roadster
唸るbooster
Hitting that booster
flow glow the space to be
今chase me
Now chase me
ターボ付きスーパーカー
A turbocharged supercar
ハンドル捌きはシューマッハ
And skills like Schumacher
副操縦士はチュバッカ
Co-driver is Chewbacca
次元が違う連中ばっか
Not on my level are these suckers
コーナー攻めてるギリギリ
Braking at the last minute
モーター全開地響き
The motors whining to keep with it
空から導き
A lead from the sky, it's complicit
お肌がピチピチ
Skin like Venus, we bring it
タイヤ焦がしてドーナツターン
Tires smoking during a donut
弾き飛んでくドラム缶
Barrels flying up and about
顧客満足度高くてぶち上がってるお客さん
Crowd's going nuts, loving every minute
0から最高到達点
Going from zero to max
ためてる太陽光発電
Charged up on solar, so relax
探索するこの小惑星
We're exploring this planet
超覚醒突入ボーナスステージ
Hit the bonus stage, now to smash it
一直線伸びている道路
A straight road to the horizon
vibrationエンジンの鼓動
Can feel the engine's vibration
速度増し上がっている高度
Speed going up, acceleration
限界重力凌駕し上昇
Shaking off our limits and gravity
開拓しまくっていくフロンティア
We're terraforming the frontier
旅立つroadster only one
The Roadster is the only one pioneer
アクセル踏み込んでくドンピシャ
Putting the pedal to the metal
飛んでく日本遺産
Japanese heritages open a portal
1億馬力の重低音
The bass packs a billion HP
火星のホテルが休憩所
A hotel on Mars is our break room
並んで走行ufo
As the UFOs race in space
降り立つ宇宙ステーション
Get a visit from the space station
物語を継承
Continuing the story, ayy
まるで旧約聖書
Like the testaments, old to new, ayy
この先何世紀も成長
For centuries, we'll have all the glory
生き延びて結果出す take off
To survive and leave a mark, take off
叶うはずはwon't stop
Dreams come true, we won't stop
心臓がモンスター
Our hearts are a monster
aliens turn it up
fg party hard
光るtesla roadster
Blingin' Tesla Roadster
heavy booster
目覚めていく本能
Awakening the instincts
青い炎
Blue blazes
bff let's go out , so get in the car
BFF, let's go out, so get in the car
0から宇宙まで囚われず
Prisoners to nothing, from naught to all creation
走るfg roadster
Speeding the FG Roadster
唸るbooster
Hitting that booster
flow glow the space to be
今chase me
Now chase me
Rock, rock, the space between us
ima change me
tame the fire and fall before my justice
final warning, you know my rage is limitless
on the advent of a new genesis i'm
infamous, yeah i get a little villainous
I get a little villainous.
look into my eyes
i'll seek you out
reveal the truth and lies that you just can't hide
clawing at the walls i feel these sick temptations
what do i have to sacrifice?
bound by a chain desiring to do it my way
this hurricane of a devastating force is coming
out of my veins feel my pulse it's rising and igniting
fire
snuff it out
walking the line on the edge of becoming what i never thought i'd be
better this than a goner
take 'em all out, renegade
walking the line fell so far into poison and i'm seeing me anew
got ya locked and i'm loaded
take 'em all out, renegade
don't care at all i'll fall deeper 'til i can't quit
never gon' stop 'cause i don't have a limit
my moral compass
is out of focus
renegade i'll make it a little wicked
the light goes out
make 'em fall down make your make your last wish
make 'em make 'em fall down then they crash
bound by a vow can i tread the waters lightly never
making a sound incognito dio light the pathway
making a sound, incognito, delight the pathway,
burning 'em out in the fallout i'll stand in the ashes
fire
snuff it out
walking the line on the edge of becoming what i never thought i'd be
better this than a goner
take 'em all out, renegade
walking the line fell so far into poison and i'm seeing me anew
got ya locked and i'm loaded
take 'em all out, renegade
don't care at all i'll fall deeper 'til i can't quit
never gon' stop 'cause i don't have a limit
my moral compass
is out of focus
renegade i'll make it a little wicked
the light goes out
tame the fire and fall before my justice
final warning, you know my rage is limitless
on the advent of a new genesis i'm
infamous, yeah i get a little villainous
the light goes out
ソラボエリドモ　ジンセイゲーム
Soraboeri domo jinsei game,
イワケメイタ　ハートニ　シタガッテ
iiwake meita haato ni shitagatte,
ゲンジツ　ワ　ハンソクナ　プロット　デス
genjitsu wa hankusoku na purotto desu.
トリツカルレル　オーバーナ　シバイ
Toritsukareru oobaa na shibai,
ヨエワリジョウズナアノコワネ
yoewari jouzu na ano ko wa ne,
ニドトカブッタネコハズセナイ
nidoto kabutta neko hazusenai.
イタミヲシッテシマッタ magician
Itami wo shitte shimatta magician,
テノウチワマダアカセナイ
te no uchi wa mada akasenai.
yellow yellow
ゼロカラループテンメツスルピリオド
zero kara ruupu tenmetsu suru piriodo.
yellow yellow
ソマルアカイケショウ
somaru akai keshou.
And if I can make it or not
たどり着いた 月に見放されても
From the world of men...
ひとりじゃないって 分かってるけど
I know I'm not alone, but...
どうしても孤独に呑まれそう
I'm about to be swallowed by solitude.
同じ場所で震えていても
Even if we tremble in the same place,
少しずつ進んでいけたらいいから 触れられなくてもここには確かな光があるんだ
As long as we keep moving forward, there's a certain light here.
ボラは散るまでずっとサバイバー
We are survivors until we scatter,
道なき道を往く
walking paths untrod.
誰もが迷える子羊なんだ 聞かせて小さなことも
Everyone's a stray sheep, so let me hear even the smallest things.
あぁ 完璧じゃなくても前を向けたのならきっと繋がっていく
Ah, even if it's not perfect, if we look ahead, we'll surely connect.
Let's enjoy the moment.
終わりのない闇の中で 俯いてはあふれ出す溜息
In the endless darkness, sighs overflow as I bow my head.
出口のないことばかりを考えてまた繰り返して
Thinking only of dead ends, I repeat it all over again.
うまく伝えられなくても 言葉を重ねてみたいんだよ
Even if I can't express it well, I want to keep stacking words.
Always be honest.
永遠に変わらないもの
Nothing will ever change that.
イエローイエロー 手を取り合えば
Yellow, yellow, taking each other's hands,
そこには理由はいらない
we don't need a reason at that place.
イエローイエロー 染まる赤い結晶
Yellow, yellow, a red crystal that stains.
Smile show jump, jump, jump!
踏み出す一歩は怖くても その先の景色見たいんだよ
Even if the first step is scary, I want to see the scenery beyond.
天使と悪魔がついているから いつでもすぐそばに
With angels and demons following, they're right by our side anytime.
あぁ 痛みの分だけ強くなれてるんだって信じてる
Ah, I believe that we can grow stronger just by the pain we feel.
Let's enjoy the moment.
知らずに「普通」の殻に囚われていた
Unconsciously trapped in the shell of "normalcy,"
無意識をそっと解放してみてみ、さぁ
try releasing that subconscious gently, come on!
Smile show jump, jump, jump!
どうかこの音を止めないで
Don't stop this sound, don't let it fly away!
Our time, yellow, yellow, let it flow, let it flow, just oh stay gold!
Our time, yellow, yellow, let it flow, let it flow, oh oh oh!
Let's enjoy the moment.
楽しかった！ReGLOSSでした、バイバーイ！
That was fun. ReGLOSS, bye-bye!
Time to open up your eyes, feel the music start to rise,
Got to break the world and let me in.
I know I was meant to be livin' life so fast and free,
I know I was meant to be living life so fast and free,
Try to keep your eyes on me,
'Cause this is where my story all begins!
Livin' it up like crazy, ready to play?
Living it up like crazy, ready to play?
Come at me, carried away,
So easy, I can't get enough!
Free as a bird, no limit, haven't you heard?
I'm fearless, get up and go, let's do this!
Watch me be your diva, I'm gonna raise your fever,
Shakin' up all the crowd, making some noise when I'm not allowed,
Livin' my life out loud,
living my life out loud,
I have awakened to wisdom beyond understanding,
(I keep indulging in my every whim) Let it out!
Don't blame me if I shine too bright
Can't help it if I start a fight
Now pay attention, please,
'Cause this is only the beginning - it's our genesis!
Coming to wreak some havoc, how do you like this plot twist?
I'm embracing my madness.
(Can you hear it?) Whispers banging down your window
Rumors reaching a crescendo,
No humble beginnings, I'm destined for great things!
I'm sure you've heard of me by now.
Midnight, draw me to the dark side,
Daylight, take me on a joyride,
My crime is my passion, I'm mayhem in action,
I know what day it is: this is our genesis.
Gonna start the rave, when I misbehave, take center stage!
Let the fun commence, but you know I'm gonna get intense,
There are loopholes unspoken; the rules can all be broken,
I'm runnin' on a rampage, the world is a blank page!
I'm writing my story in flames and in glory,
They're gonna know me by name!
Is this my promised land?
The future's in my hands.
But they don't understand that I'm a star in the making,
Awaking and taking a bow, tell me how you like me now!
Let your worries go, gonna show you how to lose control,
Ready? You've got to free your mind, leave your restraint behind,
Be outrageous, the chaos is contagious,
Come on, you know what time it is! It's our genesis!
Time to open up your eyes, feel the music start to rise,
Got to break the world and let me in.
I know I was meant to be livin' life so fast and free,
I know I was meant to be living life so fast and free,
Try to keep your eyes on me!
Tell me how you like me now
Let's celebrate the new year!
waku waku waku waku
Let your voice go and show you how
to lose control
You've got to free your mind
leave your restraint behind
be outrageous
the chaos is contagious
Come on, you know what time it is!
It's our Genesis!
Time to open up your eyes, feel the music start to rise,
Got to break the world and let me in.
How I was meant to be, living life so fast and free,
Run, keep your eyes on me,
This is our beginning,
'cause this is our beginning,
It's our Genesis!
Whispers, banging down your window,
Rumors reaching a crescendo,
No humble beginnings,
I'm destined for great things!
I'm sure you've heard of me by now.
Midnight, draw me to the dark side,
Daylight, take me on a joyride,
My crime is my passion,
I'm mayhem in action,
I know what day it is:
This is our genesis.
It's our genesis!
Tell me what time it is,
Yeah, you know what time it is,
It's our genesis!
君に届けたい
I want to reach you,
identity
世界でたった一人ボクを踏み出した
Stepping forward as the only one in this world,
おはよう! こんばんは!
Good morning! Good evening!
ボクの世界に叫んでみよう
Let's shout it out to my world!
本日のライブではどれの自分を見せるの
Which version of myself will I show in today's live?
毎回そう悩んで好きな自分になれない
Every time I worry like that, unable to love myself.
そしてある日誰かに言われた
Then one day, someone told me,
変な言葉なんてに迷っていた
getting lost in strange words.
いつも映る笑顔失わないように
So I won't lose the smile always reflected,
これ以上は期待を裏切らないと決めた
I decided not to betray expectations any further.
あふれている雑音の中この声響けるか
Can this voice resonate amidst the overflowing noise?
心に宿る声を聴いてみよう
Let's try listening to the voice dwelling in our hearts.
これはずっと見せたい自分だった
This was the self I always wanted to show,
あつまったかかえた違いがひとつになるidentity
gathered and embraced differences becoming one id:entity.
君が過ぎてやっとスポットライトに
After passing you, finally in the spotlight,
立てるけれど少しだけ怖くなった
I can stand, but I felt just a little scared.
でもね 1人じゃない仲間たちがいるんだ
But you know, I'm not alone, my friends are here.
家族みたいな絆で違いが分かりあえた
With a bond like family, we came to understand our differences.
それぞれのが輝かあってハーモニー奏でるから
Because each of us shines and plays in harmony,
手を繋いで共に夢のその方へ
holding hands together toward that side of our dreams,
精一杯の歓声を上げましょう
let's raise our voices to the absolute fullest!
幸せ音を届けるんだどこにだって響けよ
Delivering sounds of happiness, may they echo anywhere.
新しい舞台に飛び込んでいくわ
Diving into a brand new stage!
パレード パレード パレード！
Parade, parade, parade!
輝くんだよ 呼び合う声を 合図に
It's time to shine, using our calling voices as the signal!
パレード パレード パレード！
Parade, parade, parade!
探しに行く スタートは何回だって
We'll go search, no matter how many times we start over!
ブルーのハーモニーになって
Becoming a blue harmony,
心の迷いも消えていく
even the hesitation in our hearts fades away.
これからずっと この自分のままで 集まった声たちが
From now on, just as we are, the voices that gathered...
違っても 違うえも
Even if they're different, even if they diverge,
譲れないと信じて ひとつになる
believing we won't yield, we become one.
アイデンティティ
Our identity!
真っ直ぐな朝も お疲れ様でした
Straight mornings, and thank you for your hard work.
真っ直ぐな夜も また逢う日まで
Straight nights, until the day we meet again.
我ら 栄光の星をすべるもの 秘密結社
We who rule the stars of glory, Secret Society!
ホロックス参上だぜ
HoloX has arrived!
日々を尽くすだ 2026年を待て 貴様ら
Devote your days, wait for 2026, you scoundrels!
準備はいいか！？
Are you ready!?
ネクスと ネクスと ネクスと ネクスが交差する 真ん中で
In the exact center where "Next" and "Next" and "Next" and "Next" intersect,
ネクスと ネクスと ネクスと メイテインはもう 始まってる
"Next" and "Next" and "Next" and the making has already begun!
夜が深まる闇夜の darkness
The darkness of the deep night...
ノアールたちはボンドでかくす
Noir figures hidden by bond,
縄に従えとうい skin
skin obedient to the rope,
盲人にニンサムライが居る
where the blind man and the samurai are.
夜道にしないけど
Though the path isn't dark,
ルールを破ってでしょ
we'll break the rules, won't we?
センスでボケ
Making jokes with flair,
きっと赤字じゃ言い出し
surely starting off in the red,
悪の掌 踊りたくなる
dancing in the palm of evil's hand.
ほら君も 気付けば のりのりで
Look, before you know it, you're riding the wave!
どうしょうもない どうしようもない おちてく運命
Helpless, hopeless, a descending fate.
なんたってしょうがない もってきず 塗り替えよ
No matter what, we can't help it, let's repaint everything!
エクスと エクスと エクスと エクスが交差する 真ん中で
In the exact center where "X" and "X" and "X" and "X" intersect,
ネクスと ネクスと ネクスと メイテインはもう 始まってる
"Next" and "Next" and "Next" and the making has already begun!
飛び跳ね 飛び跳ね 闇が呼ぶ方へ
Jump, jump, towards where the darkness calls!
反復の エクスです 混沌としたこの世界を
Repetitive "X", this chaotic world...
我らホロックス色に塗り替えるのだ
we'll repaint in HoloX colors!
皆のもの 掲げよ Yes My Dark!
Everyone, raise your hands: Yes My Dark!
アブソリュート ダークネス インフィニティ 来世こそ世界制服
Absolute Darkness Infinity, conquering the world in our next life!
はい、今見てる皆さんはもうホロックスサーですよ！
Yes, everyone watching right now is already a HoloX member!
隣にうまれる 2026年もずっと一緒だよ
Born side by side, we'll be together through 2026 as well!
暗闇まで 鏡びらし 一人よりは 叩き切れ
Shattering the mirrors down to the darkness, breaking through rather than being alone!
どうしょうもない どうしようもない おちてく運命
Helpless, hopeless, a descending fate.
なんたってしょうがない もぜんぶ 塗り替えよ 活目せよ
No matter what, repaint everything, feast your eyes on this!
エクスと エクスと エクスと エクスが交差する 真ん中で
In the exact center where "X" and "X" and "X" and "X" intersect,
ネクスと ネクスと ネクスと メイテインはもう 始まってる
"Next" and "Next" and "Next" and the making has already begun!
飛び跳ね 飛び跳ね 闇が呼ぶ方へ
Jump, jump, towards where the darkness calls!
反復の エクスです 混沌としたこの世界を
Repetitive "X", this chaotic world...
我らホロックス色に塗り替えるのだ
we'll repaint in HoloX colors!
皆のもの 掲げよ Yes My Dark!
Everyone, raise your hands: Yes My Dark!
アブソリュート ダークネス インフィニティ 来世こそ世界制服
Absolute Darkness Infinity, conquering the world in our next life!
Run Back 'Round
Don't Stop Now
Up with the moonlight,
Down in the street lights,
Looking for a spotlight,
Making my move
I'm running
行こう！
Let's go!
Days like a whirlwind don't stop coming,
Got me in a tailspin,
What can I do?
Keep running!
行こう！！
Let's go!!
Lost and found, back to where I started,
I won't stay down, trust me, I can do it!
I live life loud, take it to the limit,
So stand up proud, now I'm gonna sing it!
Run Back 'Round, it's a new beginning,
I run back 'round, got to keep believing,
I run back 'round, I know where I'm going,
I run back 'round, nothing's gonna stop me now!
I'm gonna run back 'round!
Sparks on the pavement,
Dreams in the distance,
Gotta be relentless,
Faster than sound.
Keep running!
Lock it and load it, 僕らはexplosive
Lock it and load it, we're explosive
Swifter and lighter, 明日もきっとbrighter
Swifter and lighter, tomorrow too will be brighter
Faster than lightning, about to get exciting
Run Back 'Round, it's a new beginning,
I run back 'round, got to keep believing,
I run back 'round, I know where I'm going,
I run back 'round, nothing's gonna stop me now!
止まらないよっ！
Nothing's gonna stop me now!
I'm gonna run Back 'Round!
I'm gonna run back 'round!
走って、走って、走って！
Running, running, running!
I'm gonna run back 'round!
始まるよ、Look at our dreams just waiting, now
It's starting, look at our dreams just waiting, now
I'm gonna run back 'round!
ハーロー！You guys ready?
Hello everyone, are you guys ready?
To greet the New Year?
Hell yeah!
No time to waste,
Let's get it started!
単純なphraseで catchして
Catch with a simple phrase
困難だらけの人生だけど
It's a difficult life, but
自由奔放にslapして楽しんじゃおう
Let's enjoy it with a free and easy slap!
Ah Oh Ah Oh
Fly like a feather soaring high!
立ちふさがる壁なんて
The wall that stands in the way
3秒でknock out
Knock out in 3 seconds!
Fly like a feather soaring high!
止まらないんじゃなくて
It's not that we won't stop,
止まれないんだ！
We can't stop!
Slap by stepで空中散歩私なりで
Slap by step, walking in the air on my own terms,
隙あらばその瞬間に完全掌握
If there's an opening, I'll seize it completely in that instant!
沼にハマっちゃうぞ！
Falling right into the trap!
One two threeで深層心理crashして
Deep psychological crash on one two three,
ツマラナイ現実を
Shooting down absurd reality
常識外れのrifleで撃ち抜いて！
With a rifle out of common sense!
Ah 極彩色争のdance floor
Ah, the extra-colorful dance floor,
単純なphraseで catchして
Catch with a simple phrase,
困難だらけの人生だけど
though it's a life full of difficulties.
自由奔放にslapして楽しんでいこう
Let's freely slap and enjoy ourselves!
ah oh ah oh
(Fly like a feather soaring high!)
首飛ぶって位も為せば成る それがtheoryさ
Even if your neck flies off, where there's a will there's a way, that's theory.
(clap your hands and stand up, please!)
追手追及言わずに着いてきて ready？ it's time for the show
Follow without a word, ready? It's time for the show.
we're ignited, and have no fear, ready to break through.
姿形は違っても同じ想いだ
Even if our forms are different, our feelings are the same.
ah oh ah oh
姿形は違っても同じ想いだ
Even if our forms are different, our feelings are the same,
そうだから……！
that's why...!
slap by stepで空中散歩 私なりで
Taking a walk in the air step by step, in my own way,
隙あらばその瞬間に完全掌握
seizing every moment completely when an opening appears.
沼にハマっちゃうぞ！
You'll get hooked into the swamp!
one two threeで深層心理 crashして
Crashing through deep psychology on one, two, three,
ツマラナイ現実を
boring reality
常識外れの rifleで 撃ち抜いて！
gets shot through with an uncommonsense rifle!
今すぐね
Right now,
私達の色に染め上げた世界を見せる！
we'll show you a world dyed in our colors!
皆様 今年のお互いの相棒は？ ですわ！
Everyone, who is your partner this year? That's right!
ふるあいデーはもっともっと盛り上がりよ ずっと見ててね
Our interaction days will get even more exciting, keep watching us!
来年もよろしくお願いします！ 良いお年を！
We look forward to next year as well! Happy New Year!
良いお年を！
Happy New Year!
皆さん 盛り上がりおめでとうございます！
Congratulations on getting hyped, everyone!
What's up Hololive English Myth, coming right at you from brand new year!
What's up, Hololive English Myth, coming right at you from the brand new year!
今年もすごい盛り上がったね 来年もよろしく！
This year got super hyped up, let's do it again next year!
We're gonna rock the world ten times harder next year! You in? Next up, Ina!
Wah, hello everyone, this is Ina! Thank you so much for a really fun 2025!
今年すごくとっても楽しかったです 来年もよろしくお願いしますね！
I had so much fun this year, I look forward to next year too!
Yeah let's go! Next is Kiara!
きらきらしたかなしきあらです！ キララしく盛り上げようぞ！
It's the sparkling Takanashi Kiara! Let's hype it up brilliantly!
大切！ ねっ！ さあ！
It's precious! Right? Now!
Let's go!
2025年 2026年 Let's go!
2025, 2026, let's go!
一緒に盛り上げようか 2026年もよろしく！
Let's hype it up together, and here's to 2026 as well!
All right, let's show 'em what we got!
there's an answer out there somewhere when the muses whisper "truth or dare?"
the hands of fate play tug-of-war but no one's keeping score
stay the course and be tenacious 'cause the future is a game of chance
the chips are down, but i'm all in i play until i win!
i'm not gonna give up now, the wheels of fortune circle back around.
a new turn in the betting ring; a maze of outcomes drawn in golden string.
and through this tangled thread, i see what's up ahead:
a wild chase, a frantic pace, i got to try my luck, i'm spinning fate
ah… la da da da da da da i'm always spinning fate whoah yeah
Ah... la da da da da da da, I'm always spinning fate, whoah yeah.
spin the roulette, see where it falls, testing the limits and betting it all—
round and around, jumping into the circle over and over, a test of will
oh, the game is never easy and the outcome is a mystery.
but these are fates worth betting on, their threads unbroken.
called to life by flaxen string, casting lots together at the start of everything.
i'm not gonna give up yet, i spin back 'round with every chance i get,
the wheel turns and the die is cast, the time has come for fate to change at last.
and if it's black or red, i'm moving up ahead! a perfect chance, a daring dance
i'll spin this thread of fate with my own hands
and through this tangled thread, i see what's up ahead
There's an answer out there somewhere
When the muses whisper "truth or dare?"
The hands of fate play tug-of-war
But no one's keeping score
Stay the course and be tenacious
'Cause the future is a game of chance
The chips are down, but I'm all in
I play until I win!
I'm not gonna give up now,
The wheels of fortune circle back around.
A new turn in the betting ring;
A maze of outcomes drawn in golden string.
And through this tangled thread, I see what's up ahead:
A wild chase, a frantic pace,
I got to try my luck, I'm spinning fate.
(Ah... La da da da da da da)
Hyper Jumpin' now
Hyper Jumpin' 飛び出そう
Hyper Jumpin'飛び出そう
Come on baby 輝いて
ハートきゅんっってPump it up
Hyper Jumpin' 夢の先まで
もっと もっと
刺激が欲しいの
Hyper Jumpin' now
Hyper Jumpin'
子どもくらいはしゃぐ方がお徳でしょう
低気圧から抜け上がっていくテンション
酔いながら打ち返しまくる (メンション)
カートを乗りこなして進むミッション
このままスピード加速して
たどり着く先に何があるんだろう
止まらない気持ちは助走つけて
次元を超えて行こう さあ
Hyper Jumpin' 飛び跳ねよう
ハイになって灰になるまで
ダンシング Shake it up
Hyper Jumpin' 空の向こうまで
もっと もっと近づきたいの
(Woh...) ドキドキしたい
Gimme gimme gimme愛
(Woh...) もっと もっと高く飛びたいの
Hyper Jumpin' now
Hyper Jumpin'
斜めから攻めて解決 (クエストション)
ネガティブを切り裂いてくれるチェーンソー
流れるコメントと掛け合いセッション
エイムを鍛えて狙い撃つ Flick shot
Disは No no 好きなら More more more
邪魔するノイズは撃ち消せ Bang bang bang
遊びたいだけ アンチは無視して
笑い飛ばして 蹴飛ばせ Kick it!!
Jump around!! Jump around!!
このまま僕らは旅をして
たどり着く先に何があるんだろう
信じた未来とリンクして
次元を超えて行こう さあ
Hyper Jumpin' 飛び越えよう
ハイになって灰になるまで
ダンシング Shake it up
Hyper Jumpin' 海の向こうまで
もっと もっと近づきたいの
(Woh...) ドキドキしたい
Gimme gimme gimme愛
(Woh...) もっと もっと高く飛びたいの
Hyper Jumpin' now
ナナメからせめてがけっつえすちょん
ネガティブを切り裂いてくれるテンソー
残されるコメントと掛け合いセッション
エイムを鍛えて狙い撃つフリッショ
Disはノーノー 好きならもっともっともっと
邪魔するノイズは撃ち消せバンバンバン
遊びたいだけ味はむしって笑い飛ばして けっとばせ キッキング
ジャンプラン ジュープラン
このまま僕らは旅をして
たどり着く先に何があるんだろう
信じた未来とリンクして
次元を超えて行こう さあ
Hyper Jumpin' 飛び越えよう
ハイになって灰になるまで
ダンシング Shake it up
Hyper Jumpin' 海の向こうまで
もっと もっと近づきたいの
(Woh...) ドキドキしたい Gimme gimme gimme愛
(Woh...) もっと もっと高く飛びたいの
Hyper Jumpin' now
ドキドキしたい 君君君愛
もっと もっと高く飛びたいの
Hyper Jumpin' now
Awakening eyes,
opening them wide.
Escaping from dreams,
the world begins to roar.
Mirrored reflections
遠くで見てますから声はかけませんが
I'm watching from afar, so I won't call out,
鏡に映る
Reflected in the mirror,
心に宿っている 小さい光
a small light dwelling in my heart.
そう 今も感じる どこか心の奥で
Yes, I still feel it somewhere deep in my heart.
夜を覚ました 忘れられない
Waking up the night, unforgettable—
浮かぶ景色 今の自分になるその前に
The scenery floats up before becoming who I am now.
夜覚ました 忘れられない
Waking the night, unforgettable,
浮かぶ夢物語
an afloat dream tale.
忘れられない
Unforgettable—
今の自分になるその前に 涙のない ネイロでも良い
even a tearless tone is fine.
涙のない ネイロでも良い
Even a tearless tone is fine.
そして足音が落ちてくる
And footsteps come falling down.
どこまでも 引き締める鎖が
The tight chains going anywhere
あなたの体を止めてた ためらいを覚えてしまって
stopped your body, remembering hesitation
凍えていくの 飲み込んだ思い出をしまって
and freezing, putting away swallowed memories.
凍えていくの
freezing over,
足の向こう側には 未知なるエリア
beyond your feet lies an unknown area.
その交差点の先にあるのは
What lies beyond that intersection
一期一会のはじめ
is the beginning of a once-in-a-lifetime encounter.
遠くで見てますから 声はかけませんが
I'm watching from afar, so I won't call out,
楽園の底へと 落ちていく
falling toward the depths of paradise.
実感し知らぬ 時計の針の音
The sound of clock hands I've never truly realized—
経って行かなく 日常に残り
As time passes, the remaining strength...
広がる海 届く言葉も知らない森の中に
Crossing the universe, running around in panic,
宇宙を越え 逃げ惑って そんな過去も まだ 頭に響いている
such a past still echoes in my head.
ほぐれない鎖を断ち 切れないまま もがいている 物語の始まり 探し続けたい
Wanting to keep searching for the start of the story.
夢中一度の 深いカイナ 謎のようなことさ この体の中で 目覚めた
Awakening inside this body—
本当の姿
my true form.
運命の カードが あなた見なら 心を奪え
The cards of fate—if they look at you, capture your heart!
お前よあな
You are...
解き放った鎖が 消え 進めると信じて
Believing I can move forward as the freed chains vanish,
新たな自分になって 光の方へ
toward the light!
ついに辿り着いた 未知なるエリア
Finally reaching an unknown area,
その交差点を超える日が来た
the day has come to cross that intersection.
一期一会のはじめ
The beginning of a once-in-a-lifetime encounter.
信じ合う仲間と一緒に
Together with friends who trust each other,
挑戦の狼煙を上げよう 終わらない青春に
let's raise the beacon of challenge to an endless youth!
wow
Woah,
boys & girls
羞恥心は捨てて hey jump！
throw away your shyness, hey jump!
みんなで揃えれば cool jump！ jump！
aligning together for a cool jump, jump!
光る水滴こぼれ落ちて 青春感じてる猛暑日
Glowing water droplets spilling down, feeling youth on a scorching day.
あっちゅ～！ 成長した姿を見せたい リハは完璧 本番はもっと全力で high！ high！
Ah-chuu! We want to show how we've grown; rehearsal is perfect, the real show with even more full power, high! high!
夢見る空へ吸い込まれ落ちて
Sucked into the dreamy sky and falling,
青春感じているままで走り出せ
Run out while still feeling the prime of youth.
成長した姿を見せたい
I want to show you how much I've grown.
扉は完璧
The door is perfect,
本拠地はもっと全力で
our base is with even more full force,
ハイハイフー！
hi, hi, woo!
大切な思い出だってあるけどねまだ
I have precious memories too, but still...
感情に浸ってる暇はない
There's no time to be lost in emotion,
今世紀最大の夏が始まる
the biggest summer of the century begins!
想像の果てにある高み
The heights at the end of our imagination—
勝ち取った景色は尊い
the scenery we won is precious.
逃げるな 限界の壁越えて
Don't run away, cross the wall of limits!
僕らはまだチャレンジャー
We are still challengers,
イェイ！
yeah!
冷たい声に溺れてだって
Even if we drown in cold voices,
確かな望みをたぐり寄せるように
trying to pull in a faint hope—
期待外れだと
"You fell short of expectations,"
誰かが嘆く 痛いと痛いがいつも戦う
someone laments. Pain and pain always fight;
プライドだけを頼りに抗う 自分を信じたい
relying only on pride, we resist, wanting to believe in ourselves.
努力は報われる
"Efforts will be rewarded,"
笑いたい奴は笑ってろ
laugh all you want, those who want to laugh.
感情に浸ってる暇はない
There's no time to be lost in emotion,
今世紀最大の夏が始まる
the biggest summer of the century begins!
反響が足りない もっともっと
The echo isn't enough, more and more!
後悔はさせない
I won't let you regret it!
想像の果てにある高み
The heights at the end of our imagination—
勝ち取った景色は尊い
the scenery we won is precious.
逃げるな 限界の壁越えて
Don't run away, cross the wall of limits!
僕らはまだチャレンジャー
We are still challengers,
イェイ！
yeah!
重ねた手は ギュッと離さずに
Holding our stacked hands tightly without letting go,
行こう 夢見る空へ
let's go to the dreamy sky!
窓越しに見上げた
Looking up through the window,
とても小さな空
such a tiny sky—
ここで出会えたのは 数えきれない奇跡
finding you here is an uncountable miracle.
繰り返した一歩が
Every repeated step
煌めきを繋いで 星のような笑顔導いた
connects the sparkle, guiding us to a star-like smile.
Day by day
みんなの声が力になる
everyone's voice becomes our strength!
Stage by stage
それぞれ目指すもの それぞれ描くもの
each with their own goal, each painting their own dream.
それぞれ願い叶う夢へ
To the dream where each wish comes true—
重ねた手は ギュッと離さずに
Holding our stacked hands tightly without letting go,
一人ひとり違う色で描き出す
painting with each person's unique color,
ときめき
that throbbing excitement!
振り返ることなく まっすぐに
Moving straight ahead without looking back—
行こう 夢見る空へ
let's go to the dreamy sky!
笑い合ったことや 寄り添い合わない我が強い
The times we laughed together, our stubbornness when we didn't cuddle up—
思い出いっぱいなのに
even though we have so many memories!
あと少しの日々
Just a few more days
若くじゃなくって
Not just being young,
名前つけて保存
Name and save them all.
どれも全部 大事って
Saying every single one is precious,
言い切れる
I can state it proudly.
Oh! Yeah!
みんなの為が 力になる
Everyone's strength becomes power,
Oh! Yeah!
今日は 賑やかすぎるくらい
Today is almost too lively,
笑顔がもう止まらない
And our smiles won't stop.
想いは 膨らんでいく
Our feelings keep growing.
重ねた今 きっと 噛み締めた
The present we piled up, we surely savored.
ひとりひとり 違う声で 歌声は広がる
Each with a different voice, our singing spreads.
風を感じたら まっすぐに
When we feel the wind, straight ahead,
行くよ！行こう！
Let's go! Let's go!
夢見る空へ
To the dreaming sky!
憧れで伸ばし
Reaching out with longing,
掴み取った その光だ
That light we grasped with both hands.
いつの日か また誰かの 憧れに変わる 繋ぎよ
Someday turning into someone else's longing, let's connect.
重ねた手は ぎゅっと
Our clasped hands tightly...
重ねた手は ぎゅっと離さずに
Without ever letting go of our clasped hands,
ひとりひとり 違う色で描き出す ドキドキ
Each painting in different colors, heartbeat.
出逢ったすべてに ありがとう
Thank you for everything we've met.
奇跡だって起こし続け
Continuing to make miracles happen,
ずっと側にいるよ 行くよ！行こう！
I'll always be by your side. Let's go!
夢見る空へ
To the dreaming sky!
ホロライブゲーマーズ！
Hololive GAMERS!
We are GAMERS !!!!
みんなお待たせ！
Everyone, thanks for waiting!
We are GAMERS !!!! 楽しむ準備は できてるよね？
We are GAMERS !!!! Are you ready to have fun?
せーの！ We are GAMERS !!!!
Ready, set! We are GAMERS !!!!
ふゆーん！
Fuyuun!
おっきなキツネが 登場 白髪もみ毛耳 白髪もみ毛吹雪で
A big fox appears—white hair, sideburns, ears, a blizzard!
突っ込んじゃ おしまい！ 君はスコーピオン ニュウ星のさい
Plunging right in! You're a scorpion on New Star!
入店！イエーイ！ココンと出迎こ、ちょうだい！
Entering! Yay! Welcome us with a "kokon"!
え？あいじゃない？ しっとり言うわ MC お前のやりきった顔が惜しい！
Eh? Isn't that love? Softly spoken MC, what a shame!
みおん！ ぶちぶちぶちなのよ 狼耳尾だよ 黒髪毛耳 狼
Mion! Breaking it down, wolf ears & tail, black hair!
突っ込んでとめます ライカム お笑いダースト 止まらない ケラケラ
Slamming on the brakes, comedy dust that won't stop, giggling.
つまり実は ポンコツドドド 壊して踏んじゃおうと
In other words, actually a clumsy dododo, smashing and stepping on it.
タロット占いで 見る未来 ほらゲーモア やりたくない！
Looking at the future through tarot, look, Gamer, I don't want to do this!
読み運 揃えれば まず最強 君も朝から ヤピタシュ
Align your luck, first strongest, you too from morning yapitashu.
クリアを目指して レベルアップ あげんきょうは なにくらい？
Aiming to clear, level up, what kind of today is it?
しんよう 君のハートも コーデしちゃう 接客をしてシンギュレーション
Trusting, we'll coordinate your heart too, service and singularity.
初見も常連も こたつも 対応よ パリピゲームは 楽しいね
First-timers, regulars, and kotatsu welcomed, party games are fun!
We are GAMERS !!!!
おかゆー！
Okayu!
いつももくもく 猫またおかゆ おにぎり おにぎり 配達だ
Always quiet, Nekomata Okayu, delivering rice balls.
キラキラ ふろふろ 小生意気な 猫だもん おっそっか ぼくで良くない？
Sparkling, bath-loving, cheeky cat, isn't it fine to be me?
まったり ゆっくり ほねるリズム 全肯定する おかゆイズム 全肯定 コーリズオーケー
Relaxed, slow rhythm, totally affirming Okayuism, all is okay.
毎日僕と いっしょ！
Every day together with me!
ころねー！
Korone!
おはよ 指指まわ ファンはこれこれ 犬神からね
Morning, spinning fingers, fans are this, Inugami Korone.
剣士 キャバリア キングチャールズ スパニエル プック ケド アズカケル
Swordsman, Cavalier, King Charles Spaniel, pluck ked azukakeru.
生まれる イントネーション 笑える リアクション まずは指を捧げてくれる？ はい師匠！
Raw intonation, funny reaction, first will you offer your fingers? Yes, Master!
分かったの 褒め死にじゅうちょう けものっ子のでざろけ お届け
Understood, praising to death, beast girl delivery.
Parade, Parade, Parade!
輝くんだよ 呼び合う声を
Shining bright, using our calling voices
合図に
as the signal
Parade, Parade, Parade!
探しにいくよ スタートは何回だって
Searching for it, starts are countless times!
何プレイしよう? 今日は
What shall we play today?
君のハートを 回復しちゃう
I'll heal your heart!
わくわくするね この感情
My heart is pounding with excitement,
耐えきれないって やめられないだって
I just can't resist, I can't stop!
ゲームが好きなんだもん
Because I love games!
外伝ですが ボーナスチャレンジの時間です
This is a side story, but it's Bonus Challenge time!
大きな声でレスポンスして 高得点を狙いましょう
Let's respond loudly and aim for a high score!
Are you ready?
成功、ドーン！
Success, boom!
コン、コン！
Kon, kon!
生、にゃお、にゃお！
Sei, nyao, nyao!
にゃお、にゃお！
Nyao, nyao!
性、もぐ、もぐ！
Sei, mogu, mogu!
もぐ、もぐ！
Mogu, mogu!
性、ゆび、ゆび！
Sei, yubi, yubi!
ゆび、ゆび！
Yubi, yubi!
成功、ドーン！
Success, boom!
コン、コン！
Kon, kon!
生、にゃお、にゃお！
Sei, nyao, nyao!
にゃお、にゃお！
Nyao, nyao!
性、もぐ、もぐ！
Sei, mogu, mogu!
もぐ、もぐ！
Mogu, mogu!
性、ゆび、ゆび！
Sei, yubi, yubi!
ゆび、ゆび！
Yubi, yubi!
Parade, Parade, Parade!
輝くんだよ 呼び合う声を 合図に
Shining bright, using our calling voices as the signal
Parade, Parade, Parade!
うまくいかなくってもコンティニュー
Even if things don't go well, continue!
粘りぬくまで 諦めないエンディング
Never giving up until the very end, that's the ending!
を見に行こう
Let's go see it!
君のハートも 攻略しちゃう
We'll conquer your heart too!
選択をして シミュレーション
Making our choice, simulation!
初見もこそだん もた、いよりゃーば
First-timers and veterans alike, no matter who you are,
ゲーマーは楽しみね
Gamers know how to have fun!
ゲ、ゲームは楽しぃね
Ga, gaming is fun!
We are GAMERS!
こうして2025年の幕が閉じるのであった
And thus, the curtain on 2025 closed.
生まれ立てのドキドキを響かせよう
Let's make our newborn heartbeats resound!
最高の時間 最高の仲間と キラメキの昨日手
With the best time and best friends, into yesterday's sparkle...
キラメキライダー☆
Kirameki Rider☆
覚えているかな 最初の歌
Do you remember our very first song?
懐かしいね 私の声が 震えていた
It brings back memories, my voice was trembling.
音楽く星 あの日から続く未来は
That musical star, the future continuing from that day,
みんなと掴んだ今日だよ
is today that we grabbed together with everyone!
もっともっともっと 加速するハート
Accelerating heart, ever faster and faster!
一緒に行くよ どこまでも
We'll go together, no matter how far!
準備はOK?
Are you ready?
開け 夢の扉を
Open the door of dreams!
1・2・3・キラメキナイト
One, two, three, Kirameki Night!
生まれ立てのドキドキを響かせよう
Let's make our newborn heartbeats resound!
最高の時間 最高の仲間と
With the best time and best friends!
ここにいるよ 見つけてくれたから
I'm right here because you found me,
君に会いたくて やってきたんだ
I came here because I wanted to see you!
みんなで歌おう 終わらないメロディ
Let's sing together, an endless melody,
キラメキ日和のって
on a sparkling, sunny day!
届いてるかな 私の声
I wonder if my voice is reaching you,
はっきりと届けたいのは 君に笑顔
what I want to clearly deliver is your smile!
理想の高さに 負けずして みんなと泣き笑いね
Without yielding to high ideals, crying and laughing with everyone!
ぎゅっとぎゅっとぎゅっと すべてを抱きしめて
Hugging everything tightly, tightly, tightly,
一緒に行こう どこまでも
let's go together, no matter how far!
準備はOK?
Are you ready?
進め 希望の道を
Advance on the path of hope!
1・2・3・キラメキナイト
One, two, three, Kirameki Night!
好きな気持ちから ふるに奏でたいな
I want to play to the fullest from my favorite feelings,
最高の場所 最高のみんなと
in the best place with everyone!
ここにいるよ 幻なんか
I'm right here, it's no illusion!
パレード パレード パレード！
Parade, parade, parade!
君の心が 幸せに染まるように
So that your heart is dyed with happiness,
重ねていくハーモニー きらめき纏って
piling up harmonies and draping ourselves in sparkle!
きらめき纏って
Draped in sparkle!
歌い続けたいな
I want to keep on singing,
踊り続けたいな
I want to keep on dancing.
そんな願いは わがままもいいでしょ
Such wishes, even if selfish, are fine, right?
だって楽しすぎて も止まらない
Because it's too much fun and won't stop!
輝くステージで求め合って
Seeking each other on the shining stage,
ずっとずっと
always and forever!
嬉しい 楽しい 愛しいだけじゃ語れない
Can't describe it with just happy, fun, and lovely,
今も 今も 悩みはあるけど
Even now, even now, there are worries, but...
ここにいるよ 私 ここにいるよ
I'm here, I'm right here!
君と同じ世界を見つめて
Gazing at the same world as you,
いっそきらめき纏って
I'd rather wrap myself in sparkle.
生まれたてのドキドキも響かせよう
Let's make our newborn heartbeats resonate too!
最高な時間 最高な仲間と
With the best time and best friends,
ここにいるよ 見つけてくれたから
I'm here, because you found me.
君に会いたくてやってきたんだ みんなで歌おう
I came here because I wanted to see you, let's all sing together!
終わらないメロディ きらめき纏って
An endless melody, draped in sparkle,
きらめき纏って
draped in sparkle!
2025年もあと少し！
2025 is almost over!
みんな盛り上がってる？
Are you all getting hyped?
今回はカウントダウンライブ！
This time it's the countdown live!
あれれ？ ごめん、今年の残り時間少なくない！？
Huh? Wait, isn't the remaining time of this year short?!
まだまだ足りない！こんなのやだ！
Still not enough! I hate this!
電脳ぴゅあ推し大宣言
Cyber Pure Oshi Grand Declaration!
推し変は許しません
Changing your oshi is not forgiven!
私だけに注目してね
Pay attention only to me!
私だけにヒットして！ 倒しちゃお、君がヤバイヤバスタッグ超！
Hit only on me! Take them down, you're in big trouble, super!
深くマークして ちょっとちょっとも もう許さないでしょ？
Mark me closely, you won't even forgive a little bit, right?
アップアップ！ 吸い込む空気、あたしのものにしたいの！
Up up! I want to make the air I breathe mine!
いつも見て見て 私も合ってる？
Always watch me, am I doing it right?
あなたが推してくれる愛情のセンター！
The center of love that you root for!
私の架け橋 栄光ソラ！
My bridge, glorious Sora!
ラビラビラビュ！ 私死六時中ちゅうちゅう
Laby-laby-labyu! I'm sucking up to you around the clock!
とことことことこ とっても愛して ほしいのピピハピハピピ！
Walking step by step, I want you to love me so much, pipi-hapi-hapipi!
はっきりはっきりはっきりはっきり 心踊らせて ピコピコ気持のバロメーターが超上がる！
Clearly making my heart dance, the pikopiko emotion meter shoots way up!
あしたもきっと愛し愛され わかりあっていよね？
Tomorrow too, we'll love and understand each other, right?
おおいにゃ、ここまできついてこれてる？
Hey meow, can you keep up this far?
このあともこの調子でいくよー！
We'll keep going at this pace after this too!
うりゃおい！うりゃおい！うりゃおい！うりゃおい！
Urya-oi! Urya-oi! Urya-oi! Urya-oi!
心変わりなんて他の子褒めるのよそ見 気を抜くな集中！
Changing your oshi, praising other girls, looking away—don't lose focus, concentrate!
私以外が今気になってるでしょ？
You're interested in someone else right now, aren't you?
あり得ない あり得ない (パンパン！) 他の子にちょっとだけよろみしたよね？嘘まじり？でしょ？
No way, no way! You flirted a little with another girl, didn't you? Mixed with lies? Right?
今は落ち込んでる私をそんじゃ指切りしてよ ハリセンボン！
Now make a pinky promise with gloomy me, Senbonzakura!
心変わりしたら本当に詰めるお仕置き泣いちゃうからね？
If you change your oshi, I'll really punish you, you'll cry, you know?
おしおきはしてないね 私だけに少しして
You haven't been punished yet, right? Do it just to me a little.
たてよほら褒め言葉愛にあふれている
Stand up, look, words of praise are overflowing with love.
星のHP みるみる回復 秘密のレチなパワチャージ！
Star's HP recovering instantly, secret retina power charge!
ごめごめごめちょ よそ見したら ぷんぷんぷんめっ！
Sorry sorry sorry-cho, if you look away, pun-pun-pun-met!
メロメロメロポ ププププラーン ピラメキトシマショ
Mero-mero-mero-po, pupupu-plann, let's make it a flash!
おしおきはしてないね 私だけに少しして 私だけに少しして
You haven't been punished yet, do it just to me, just to me a little...
だってほら褒め言葉愛にあふれている
Because look, words of praise are overflowing with love!
星のHP みるみる回復 秘密のレチなパワチャージ！
Star's HP recovering instantly, secret retina power charge!
ごめごめごめちょ よそ見したら ぷんぷんぷんめっ！
Sorry sorry sorry-cho, if you look away, pun-pun-pun-met!
ラビラビラビュ！ 私死六時中ちゅうちゅう…
Laby-laby-labyu! I'm sucking up to you around the clock...
は～い、これから配信始めるよ
Hey! We're starting the stream now!
みんな観てる？
Are you all watching?
今回はコラボ配信！
This time it's a collab stream!
あれ？あれれ～？？
Huh? Wait a second, what?
コメントの熱量、なんだか少なくない？？？
The chat's heat feels a bit low, doesn't it?
まだまだ足りないっ！！
It's still not enough!
こんなののう～～ん！！！
Like this!
推し変は許しませんっ！！
Changing oshi is unforgivable!
『わ・た・し』だけに尽くしてね♡
Devoted only to "me"! ♡
わたしだけにひと筋
Only for me, single-minded devotion.
単推しじゃなきゃヤダヤダ
If you only like me!
他の子にちょちょちょちょっとでも
Even just a tiny bit for other girls,
よそ見をしたら
if you look away—
ぷんぷんぷん 滅！！
Puny puny puny, exterminate!!
滅！！！
Exterminate!!!
めらめらメンヘラップ
Messy men-heala-p!
ほっぺふくらむ
Cheek blushing,
にらめっこしましょ
let's get sloppy-happy!
あっっぷっぷ ぷいっ！！
Up-up-ppy!!
プクッ怒顔も かわいいでしょ？！
Even pouting angry faces are cute, right?!
同じ未来を見たい
I want to see the same future,
あの夢手にしたい
I want to make that dream mine.
それぞれ違った
With our own different hearts,
心で走れ Go!
let's run, Go!
どこを見ても真っ暗な場所に芽生えてたほんの小さな希望にこの瞳うばわれてた
No matter where I look, in pitch darkness a tiny hope sprouted,
Shiny Smily Story
不安で揺れる心をうまくチューニングして
Tuning my shaking heart with anxiety just right,
ほんの小さな勇気を振り絞っていたよ
I mustered up just a tiny bit of courage.
諦めの文字ないとして進む苦しい時も
Even through difficult times without words of surrender,
もう私は一人じゃないから
I'm no longer alone.
だからもっと夢追いかけたい わくわく止まらない
That's why I want to chase my dreams even more, the excitement won't stop.
想像越えてく世界見せてあげる
I'll show you a world beyond imagination.
アクセスしてみたい 後悔なんてそうさせない
I want to access it, I won't let you regret it.
それぞれ違った心で走れ Go!
Let's run with our respective different hearts, Go!
仮想の空に輝くまぶしい想いは
Shining dazzling thoughts in a virtual sky
見たことのない光をリアルに届けるよ
deliver unseen light to the real world.
いつも聴こえるエールをここにキャプチャして
Capturing the cheering we always hear right here,
また新しい光を探したくなる
I want to search for a brand new light,
キミの笑顔を保存して進む
and save your smile.
悲しい時に見返すよ力があふれから
When things get sad, looking back gives me strength.
胸を張って夢追いかけたい 奇跡のストーリー
Standing proud to chase our dreams—a miracle story.
一緒に作ろう終わらない夢を
Let's create an endless dream together.
誰一人欠かせない愛が待ったこの世界
A world where love awaits, leaving no one behind.
それぞれ違った心でいろどり
With our respective different hearts, let's color it in.
かなしいときもさみしいときも
Even in sad times, even in lonely times,
信じあえるものがある
there is something we can believe in together.
忘れずにこの鼓動鳴らし続けたい
I want to keep ringing this heartbeat without forgetting.
終わらない世界に溢れ出してく笑顔たち
Overflowing into an endless world, smiles spilling out,
憧れの舞台立ちたいらしく輝きたい
wanting to stand on that yearning stage, wanting to shine brightly.
ときに涙してまた笑い合いたい
Sometimes shedding tears, but then laughing together again.
同じ未来を見たい
I want to see the same future,
あの夢手にしたい
I want to make that dream mine,
踏み出そう奇跡の一歩を
taking that miraculous first step.
息きらして夢追いかけたい わくわく止まらない
Breathlessly chasing dreams, the excitement won't stop,
想像越えてく世界見せてあげる
showing you a world beyond imagination.
アクセスしてみたい 後悔なんてここにない
Wanting to try accessing it, no room for regrets,
それぞれ違った心で作る World
creating a world with our respective different hearts.
胸を張って夢追いかけたい 奇跡のストーリー
Standing proud to chase our dreams—a miracle story,
一緒に作ろう 終わらない夢を
let's create an endless dream together.
誰一人欠かせない愛が待ったこの世界
A world where love awaits, leaving no one behind,
それぞれ違った心でいろどり
with our respective different hearts, let's color it in.
かなしいときもさみしいときも
Even when sad, even when lonely,
信じあえるものがある
if there is something we can truly believe in together,
この鼓動をならし続けたい
we can continue chaining this joy smoothly.
忘れかけた世界に溢れ出してく笑顔たち
The forgotten world is overflowing with smiles,
憧れの舞台立ちたいらしく輝きたい
wanting to stand on that yearning stage and shine brightly.
ときに涙してまた笑い合いたい
Sometimes shedding tears, but then laughing together again.
同じ未来を見たい
I want to see the same future,
あの夢手にしたい
I want to make that dream mine.
踏み出すよ奇跡の一歩を
Stepping forward, taking that miraculous step,
息きらして夢追いかけたい わくわく止まらない
breathlessly chasing dreams, the excitement won't stop.
想像越えてく世界見せてあげる
Showing you a world beyond imagination,
アクセスしてみたい 後悔なんてここにない
wanting to try accessing it, no room for regrets,
それぞれ違った心で作る World
creating a world with our respective different hearts.
胸を張って夢追いかけたい 奇跡のストーリー
Standing proud to chase our dreams—a miracle story,
一緒に作ろう 終わらない夢を
let's create an endless dream together.
誰一人欠かせない愛が待ったこの世界
A world where love awaits, leaving no one behind,
それぞれ違った心でいろどり
with our respective different hearts, let's color it in.
作ろう
Let's build it together!
みんな！コークは持ったかな？
Everyone! Did you get your Coke?
準備した！乾杯するー！
Ready! Let's toast!
こらこら、早いはずだよ！
Hey hey, that's too early!
よけるな！当たる！少し越しのタイミングで、みんなで乾杯ってするんだよ！
Don't dodge! It'll hit! Right before the countdown, everyone toasts together!
やだやだ、もう喉カラカラ！
No way, my throat is already parched!
楽しみだねえ
How exciting~
ねえ、みこさん？みこさん？
Right, Miko-san? Miko-san?
いいライブだったね
It was a good live.
お疲れ様
Good work.
このあとどうする？
What should we do after this?
お寿司食べる？
Eat sushi?
いや、どこも混んでんじゃない？
No, isn't everywhere crowded?
確かに。お腹減りましたね
True. We must be hungry.
あ、運転手さんまっすぐね
Ah, driver straight ahead.
おーおー
Oh oh.
おまえら！
You guys!
何やってんだ！乾杯乾杯！
What are you doing! Toast, toast!
ころちゃんたちが追っかけてくる
Korone and the others are chasing us.
あらあら、ころちゃんたちお腹空いちゃいちゃったのかな？
Oh my, did Korone and the others get hungry?
なんか怒ってない？
Aren't they mad?
え？あ、やばい
Eh? Ah, oh no.
あのいたずら積もれたかな？
Did those pranks pile up?
やりすぎだったかも。やばい顔も。
Maybe we went too far. What a scary face too.
運転手さん、ごめん！
Driver, sorry!
みこのドラテクで逃げるぞ！
Let's escape with Miko's driving technique!
危ない！
Watch out!
すごいすごい！
Amazing, amazing!
ころさんごめんて、もういたずらないから
Korone-san sorry, no more pranks!
だめだよみこみこ、反省しなさい
No way Miko-miko, reflect on yourself.
さっきも餃子食べたが
We already ate gyoza though.
何の話だよ
What are you talking about?
二人ともこれ持って
You two, hold this.
何するの？
What are you doing?
もうすぐ新年だよ！
It's almost New Year!
乾杯！
Cheers!
明けましておめでとう！
Happy New Year!
今年もよろしくね
Looking forward to this year too!
コーラいっぱい！
So much Coke!
おいおい、
Hey hey,
いたずらって何なの？
what's with the pranks?
あ、それね
Ah, that?
ころさんのへそ増やしたんだよ
We increased Korone-san's belly buttons.
恐怖！
Horror!
このあとはコカ・コーラと一緒にスペシャルライブステージ！
After this, a special live stage with Coca-Cola!
イエーイ！
Yay!
そうさずっと僕らの奇跡が
That's right, our miracle will always
途切れれないように歌うんだ
keep singing on without interruption
もっと高く！大きな声で
Higher! With a louder voice
聞こえてた？何かが始まるサイン
Could you hear it? The sign that something is beginning
集まって気付けば和音を奏でた
Gathering together, before we knew it, we played a harmony
夢に見るだけじゃもう足りないでしょ？
Just dreaming isn't enough anymore, right?
キミを待ってる世界があるよ
There's a world waiting for you
楽しい予感にほら飛び乗っちゃえばいい
Come on, just jump right into this fun premonition
トキメキは止められないから走ろう！
Because excitement cannot be stopped, let's run!
連れて行くよ！光の真ん中　夢の先へ
I'll take you! Right into the center of the light, beyond dreams
羽ばたける勇気はキミの願い
The courage to spread your wings is your wish
皆で繋いだこの奇跡が
This miracle we all connected together
途切れないように歌うんだもっと高く！
will keep singing on without interruption, higher!
大きな声で
With a louder voice!
答えとか理屈に悩まされて
Troubled by answers and logic
さまよっても戻ってこれる場所があったんだ
Even if I wander, there was a place I could return to
地図にない道ゆく僕らの旅　願いだけが道標だよ
Our journey down unmapped roads, only our wishes are our guideposts
夢の色が変わっても変わらないメロディ
Even if the color of our dreams changes, the melody remains unchanged
キミのために僕らのために歌おう！
Let's sing for you, for us!
そうさきっと！僕らの奇跡は終わらないよ
That's right, surely! Our miracle will never end
涙さえキッカケに変えていこう
Let's turn even our tears into a catalyst
信じてくれる仲間と一緒にどこへだって飛び出してこう
Together with friends who believe in us, let's fly out anywhere
もっと遠く！空を越えて
Further away! Beyond the sky
未来の僕らにまだ見ぬキミに伝えたいこと沢山あるんだ
There's so much I want to tell our future selves and you whom I haven't met yet
迎えたイマは当たり前なんかなんじゃない　翼を広げさあ今飛ぼう！
The present we welcomed isn't just a given, spread your wings and let's fly now!
take my hand!! 連れて行くよ！光の真ん中　夢の先へ
take my hand!! I'll take you! Right into the center of the light, beyond dreams
羽ばたける勇気はキミの願い
The courage to spread your wings is your wish
皆で繋いだこの奇跡が途切れないように歌うんだ
This miracle we all connected together will keep singing on without interruption
もっと高く！大きな声で
Higher! With a louder voice!
僕らの未来彩ってどこまでも響け！ prism melody
Coloring our future, echoing everywhere! prism melody
そうさずっと！僕らの奇跡が
That's right, always! Our miracles
途切れぬように歌うんだ
will keep singing without end!
もっと高く！大きな声で
Higher still! With a loud voice,
聞こえてた？何か始まるサイン
could you hear it? A sign that something is starting.
集まって気付けばコードを奏でてた
Gathering together, before we knew it, we were playing chords.
夢に見るだけじゃもう物足りないでしょう？
Just dreaming isn't enough anymore, right?
君を待ってる世界があるよ
There's a world waiting for you,
楽しい予感にほら飛び乗っちゃえばいい
so come on, just jump on board this fun premonition!
ドキメミは止められないから
Because our excitement can't be stopped,
走ろう！
let's run!
未来の僕らに まだ見ぬ君に
To our future selves, to you whom we haven't met yet,
伝えたいこと たくさんあるんだ
we have so many things we want to tell you.
迎えたいまは 当たり前なんかじゃない
The present we've welcomed isn't just something to be taken for granted,
翼を広げ さあ今 飛ぼう！
so spread your wings and let's fly right now!
take my hand！！ 連れていくよ
take my hand!! We'll take you along,
光の真んなか 夢のさきへ
right into the center of the light, beyond our dreams.
羽ばたける勇気は君の願い みんなで繋いだこの奇跡が
The courage to spread your wings is your wish; this miracle we connected together
途切れぬように歌うんだ もっと高く！大きな声で
will keep singing without end! Higher still! With a loud voice,
答えとか理屈に惑わされて 彷徨っても戻ってこられる場所があったんだ
even if we get lost, confused by answers or logic, there was a place we could always return to.
地図にない道行く僕らの旅 願いだけが道しるべだよ
Our journey goes down paths not found on any map; our wish is our only guidepost.
夢の色が変わっても 変わらないメロディ 君のために僕らのために歌おう！
Even if the color of our dreams changes, our melody remains unchanged. Let's sing it for you, for us!
そうさずっと！僕らの軌跡は終わらないよ
That's right, always! Our trajectory will never end,
涙さえきっかけに変えていこう
let's turn even our tears into a catalyst.
信じてくれる仲間と一緒に どこへだって飛び出していこう
Together with the friends who believe in us, let's fly out anywhere!
Won't you just forget about the past?
Cause in time it will never matter
But the love we had I'm hoping it will last
Bersama kita t'lah lewati tawa dan canda jadi memori
Together we've passed through laughter and jokes turning into memories,
Pastikan artinya kan cerahkan mu nanti
make sure its meaning will brighten your future.
To do what you were meant to do
For it's time to make it true
Together we can always stand your hand in my hand
Forever hand in hand
Tuk mulai bermimpi genggam lah yang kau cari
To start dreaming, hold on to what you're searching for,
Teriakkan la la la la la la la la la la
shout it out: la la la la la, la la la la la.
Kau takkan sendiri
You won't be alone.
It's time to show them who you are
Just shout it from the mountain high
To the sky we go We go
Bersama kita t'lah lewati tawa dan canda jadi memori
Together we've passed through laughter and jokes turning into memories,
Pastikan artinya cerahkan mu nanti
make sure its meaning will brighten your future.
To do what you were meant to do
For it's time to make it true
Together we can always stand your hand in my hand
Forever hand in hand
Tuk mulai bermimpi genggam lah yang kau cari
To start dreaming, hold on to what you're searching for,
Teriakkan la la la la la la la la la la
shout it out: la la la la la, la la la la la.
Kau takkan pernah sendiri
You will never be alone.
So go and travel far Run and show them who you are
I'll be singing
La la la la la la la la la la
Be who you meant to be
Won't you just forget about the past?
Cause in time it will never matter
But the love we had, I'm hoping it will last
Bersama kita t'lah lewati
Together we have passed through it all
Tawa dan canda jadi memori
Laughter and jokes became memories
Pastikan artinya kan cerahkan mu nanti
Make sure the meaning will brighten your days later
To do what you were meant to do
For it's time to make it true
Together we can always stand Your hand in my hand
Forever hand in hand Tuk mulai bermimpi
Forever hand in hand, to start dreaming
Genggam lah yang kau cari
Grasp what you are looking for
Teriakkan
Shout it out
La la la la la
Kau takkan sendiri
You will never be alone
It's time to show them who you are
Just shout it from the mountain high
To the sky we go We go
Bersama kita t'lah lewati
Together we have passed through it all
Tawa dan canda jadi memori
Laughter and jokes became memories
Pastikan artinya cerahkan mu nanti
Make sure the meaning will brighten your days later
Cerahkan mu nanti
Brighten your days later
To do what you were meant to do
For it's time to make it true
Just look around and see—it's so incredible!
So many smiles in a sea of light
Take one step with me and you'll be dazzled,
There's magic in the air tonight
The hours zoom zoom zoom
My heart goes boom boom boom
The world is brighter because you believe in me
Let's shout it loud loud loud
Our time is right now
We're on the edge of destiny
For a moment, I can dream with you
Every miracle we hoped for might come true
We come together, reaching out from far and wide,
And suddenly, you're here by my side!
When our voices and hearts unite, we're gonna shine bright!
Together, we're all for one.
The thrill of happiness is all around us!
Jump in, 'cause it's all for one
We're on our way to good times, good vibes
We'll treasure this day the rest of our lives
All that we waited for, the dream we're striving toward,
We're singing, all for one!
All for one!
Everything's in motion, Get up and start the celebration,
Come see the wonders here beyond imagination
We're joining hands for the world to see
Feel the love and the energy!
The hours zoom zoom zoom
My heart goes boom boom boom
A dizzy whirlwind of dreams and reality
Let's shout it loud loud loud
Our time is right now
We're here together, finally!
Every moment takes my breath away;
There's a feeling here that words cannot convey,
We hear the rhythm and we rise to meet the song,
And suddenly, our hearts beat as one!
Every voice ringing loud and clear, so glad to be here
Together, we're all for one.
We'll sing in harmony and we'll be happy
Jump in, 'cause it's all for one
Keep up the hype, it's good times good vibes
Remember this night the rest of our lives
Raise up your hands and sway, your light will lead our way,
We're shining, all for one!
All for one!
So bring your memories, your joy and your hope,
We'll gather and we'll sing upon this endless road, oh, oh
Feel the music in your passionate soul,
We're here right now, so let the good times roll, oh, oh
Every time that I'm with you,
I could swear it's like a wish is coming true
So I'll believe in you if you believe in me,
Together we can chase all our dreams!
(1, 2, 3, 4, 5!)
When our voices and hearts unite, we're gonna shine bright!
Together, we're all for one.
The thrill of happiness is all around us!
Jump in, 'cause it's all for one
We're on our way to good times, good vibes
We'll treasure this day the rest of our lives
All that we waited for, the dream we're striving toward,
We're singing, all for one!
All for one!
皆さん、あけましておめでとうございます！
Happy New Year, everyone!
リグロスロードストー... リグロス！
ReGLOSS Roadst... ReGLOSS!
ここからはホロライブデヴァイスコラボステージです！聞いてください、「FG ROADSTER by ReGLOSS」！
Next is the Hololive DEV_IS collab stage! Please listen to "FG ROADSTER by ReGLOSS"!
レッツゴー！
Let's go!
搭載V8エンジン (brr, brr)
Equipped with a V8 engine (brr, brr)
第7感持ってる原人 (mm, mm)
A hominid with a 7th sense (mm, mm)
ロックするこの世界と全人類 この5人でゲームをチェンジ (aye)
Locking onto this world and humanity, 5 of us change the game (aye)
唸る4輪発射寸前
Four roaring wheels about to launch,
皆さんサンキュー散乱Hit
Thank you everyone, scattered hits,
操る2体のターントゥール
Operating two turntables,
獲る1番ここからground zero
Claiming number one right from ground zero.
リスク超えて挑戦
Challenging beyond the risk,
チャンスもセットだ当然
Opportunities are set of course,
登り上げる頂点
Climbing up to the summit,
座布団積んでく笑点
Stacking cushions for points,
乗り込むFG ROADSTER
Riding in the FG ROADSTER.
特殊部隊集合能力者
Special forces assemble, capable ones,
この歴史に名を刻む彫刻家
Sculptors carving names into history,
ぶっちぎりで置き去り後続車
Leaving trailing cars far behind.
今高速でぶっちぎっていく大気圏
Now rushing through the atmosphere at high speed,
エンジンからジェットの炎揺れている怪気炎
Jet flames shaking from the engine with blazing spirit,
眼下に見える大地を超えていく回帰線
Crossing the tropic line beyond the earth seen below,
バックミラーにbig blueが映ってるIBM
Big blue reflecting in the rearview mirror, IBM
打ち上げ台から飛んでくうちゅうら世代この燃料は
Flying off the launch pad, this generation's fuel,
朽ち果てないです銀河で寿司食べたい
Never decaying, want to eat sushi in the galaxy,
描いてるでかいビジョン燃えてるメンバー一同
Drawing a big vision, all members on fire,
ただいま現在進行形超えてくる世界規模
Currently in progress, transcending world scale.
叶えるはずだwon't stop 心臓がモンスター
It's bound to come true, won't stop, heart is a monster,
aliens turn it up, FG party hard
光るtesla roadster, heavy booster
shining tesla roadster, heavy booster,
目覚めていく本能青い炎
Awakening instinct, blue flame,
BFF, let's go out, so get in the car
0から宇宙まで囚われず
From 0 to space without being captive,
走るFG ROADSTER, 唸るbooster
Running FG ROADSTER, roaring booster,
Flow Glow the space to be, 今chase me
Flow Glow the space to be, now chase me.
ターボ付きスーパーカー
Supercar with a turbo,
ハンドル握りはシューマッハ
Steering wheel handled by Schumacher,
副操縦士はチューバッカ
Co-pilot is Chewbacca,
次元が違う連中ばっか
All guys from different dimensions.
コーナー攻めてるギリギリ
Attacking the corners by a hair,
モーター全開地鳴り
Motor at full throttle making ground rumble,
空から導き
Guidance from the sky,
お肌がピチピチ
Skin is tight and fresh.
タイヤ焦がしてドーナツターン
Burning tires in a donut turn,
弾き飛んできてドラム缶
Drum cans bouncing off,
顧客満足度高くてぶち上がってるお客様
High customer satisfaction, customers hyped up,
0から最高到達点
From zero to the highest peak,
ためしてる太陽光発電
Trying out solar power generation,
探索するこの小惑星
Exploring this asteroid,
超覚醒突入ボーナスステージ
Super awakening entry bonus stage.
あけましておめでとうございます！
Happy New Year!
ここからは私たちフロウグロウがリグロス先輩のフィーリングラデーションをかまさせていただきます！
Next, we, Flow Glow, will rock ReGLOSS-senpai's "Feelingradation"!
my heart starts skipping a beat
紐解いた新章
Unraveling a new chapter,
様変わりしてゆくshow time
A transforming show time.
全然悪くないイマジネーション
Not bad at all, this imagination,
視界の霧は晴れ渡って
The fog in our vision clears away.
悲しみに名残を告げる
Bidding farewell to sorrow,
酸いも甘いも宙に放り出して
Throwing both sweet and sour into the void.
染まる空　インクは薔薇色
The dyeing sky, ink is rose-colored.
どれだけ上手く魅せようとしても
No matter how well we try to charm,
キミがいなければ何の意味もない
Without you, it has no meaning at all.
擦り傷すらつかない幻想
An illusion that won't even get a scratch,
針の落ちないレコードさ
A record where the needle won't drop.
たった今止め処ない追い風にして
Making it an endless tailwind right now,
come on, let's roll
颯爽と吹き荒れる向かい風にも
Even against the gusting headwind,
ココロ惑わせて
Letting my heart waver,
飛び乗ってto the future
Jumping on board to the future,
フライングしたってalright
Even if we jumped the gun, it's alright,
restart line!!
ときめいてしまえば
Once my heart flutters,
瞬く間に広がる開放区
An open zone spreads in a flash.
一つ一つすべてがドラマ
Every single thing is a drama,
待ち焦がれたdaybreak
The daybreak we longed for.
restart line!!
代わる代わる彩るパノラマ
A changing, colorful panorama,
満ち溢れるフィーリングラデーション
An overflowing feelingradation.
始まりのその時が来た
The time of beginning has come,
nothing is impossible
マヤカシ誤魔化し効かない世界
A world where illusions don't work,
この先はまだ誰も知らない正解
The correct answer ahead that nobody knows.
傍観しているだけじゃ味気ない
Just standing by watching is bland,
リアルタイムで通じ合って
Connecting in real-time,
振り子にかけるエモーション
Emotion hanging on the pendulum.
後の祭りでもi don't mind
Even if it's too late, i don't mind,
大胆不敵なシチュエーション
A daring and fearless situation.
行けるところまで行ってみたい
I want to go as far as I can,
選択肢にないget off on the way
Not an option to get off on the way.
共に声を鳴らし
Resounding our voices together,
素肌を貫くような真っ直ぐな痛みが伴っても
Even with piercing, direct pain.
この仲間たちと最果てまでkeep running to the end
Running to the end with companions.
飛び乗ってto the future
Jumping on board to the future,
フライングしたってalright
Even if we jumped the gun, it's alright,
restart line!!
ときめいてしまえば
Once my heart flutters,
瞬く間に広がる開放区
An open zone spreads in a flash.
一つ一つすべてがドラマ
Every single thing is a drama,
待ち焦がれたdaybreak
The daybreak we longed for.
restart line!!
代わる代わる彩るパノラマ
A changing, colorful panorama,
満ち溢れるフィーリングラデーション
An overflowing feelingradation.
飛び出せyou raise me up
Jump out, you raise me up,
恐れるものはない
There is nothing to fear.
restart line!!
綺麗な朝焼けが
A beautiful morning glow
不透明な明日を照らすよ
Illuminates tomorrow's haze.
restart line!!
綺麗な朝焼けが、戸惑いの明日を照らすよ！
A beautiful morning glow illuminates tomorrow's hesitation!
restart line!!
ありがとうございましたー！
Thank you very much!
最後の曲は、「Our Bright Parade」！
The final song is "Our Bright Parade"!
Parade, parade, parade! 輝くんだよ
Parade, parade, parade! It's time to shine,
呼び合う声を合図に
Triggered by our calling voices together!
Parade, parade, parade! 探しにいく
Parade, parade, parade! We're going to search,
スタートは何回だって
No matter how many times we restart!
パレ、パレ、パレ、輝くんだよ
Parade, parade, parade, let's shine!
探しに行くよ
I'm going to search for it,
ここはラウンドだって
Because this place is a round...
ほら ひとりごと続く
Look, talking to myself continues,
ただ 始まりりたくて走った
Just running because I wanted it to start.
遠く 暗がりにとまった
Stopping far away in the dark.
それは 眩しすぎた名前
That name was way too dazzling.
それは 優しすぎる思い出
That memory was way too kind.
もっと 近づけと手を伸ばした
I reached out my hand to get closer.
思いがけず結び合った
We unexpectedly connected.
ほら 今 迷子は僕らになった
Look, now we've become lost children.
パレ、パレ、パレ、
Parade, parade, parade,
輝くんだよ
Let's shine!
悔しさもいとしさもすべておいで
Bring all the frustration and fondness too,
風 夢 羽根 跳び立てるさ
Wind, dream, feather, you can take flight!
途絶えない祈り光
Endless prayer light,
終わりなききざし
Endless omen,
君を見つけたこと 胸をはれるよ
I can be proud of finding you.
ここから それから
From here, and from then on,
アワプライ パレ、パレ、パレ
Our bright parade, parade, parade
だから 頼りない笑顔を
So, don't make your unreliable smile
歌おう 恥ずかしくなんてないよ
Let's sing, there's nothing to be embarrassed about.
誰もが溶ける日今まさに
The day everyone melts is right now.
いつかまた会えるおまじない
A spell so we can meet again someday.
あの日手のひらに始まったストーリー
The story that started in the palm of my hand that day.
感情いきけないことのさ、例えるような思いじゃないさ
It's not something you can just put into words, or compare easily.
ほら 今 僕らを一つと呼ぼう
Look, now let's call ourselves one.
パレ、パレ、パレ、 美しくんだよ
Parade, parade, parade, so beautifully!
許し合える切な夜はきらめく
Nights of forgiving each other sparkle.
雨晴れ、それ、また、こない空
Rain or shine, the sky that won't come again
ふさわしい旅路とは
What is a fitting journey?
君と歩くことさ
It's walking with you.
君と歩くことなんだ
It's the fact that I walk with you.
互いの前を聞けば おかえりって叫ぶよ
Whenever I hear your voice ahead, I shout 'Welcome back!'
当たり前じゃないから
Because it's not something to be taken for granted,
パレ、パレ、パレ、 輝くんだよ
Parade, parade, parade, let's shine!
暗がりを満たすのは君だ、僕だ
What fills the darkness is you, is me.
パレ、パレ、パレ、輝くんだよ
Parade, parade, parade, let's shine!
悔しさもいとしさもすべておいで
Bring all the frustration and fondness too,
風 夢 羽根 跳び立てるさ
Wind, dream, feather, you can take flight!
ささやかなのり光 終わりなききざし
A modest prayer light, an endless omen,
君と飛び込んでゆく 素敵なスタートさ
Diving in with you, what a wonderful start.
ここから それから アワプライ パレ、パレ、パレ
From here, and from then on, our bright parade, parade, parade
アワプライ パレ、パレ、パレ
Our bright parade, parade, parade
この後は もう1本グランプリ！
2026年もホロライブプロダクションをよろしくお願い致します！
Up next is another 1-Book Grand Prix!
Thank you for your continued support of hololive production in 2026!